

German Martínez QC System Technician

PHONE +34 65 28 26 499

EMAIL german.mgallardo@gmail.com

ADDRESS Barcelona, Spain

PORTFOLIO | LINKEDIN | GITHUB



SUMMARY

Fourth year physics student with prior experience in the pharmaceutical industry and advanced knowledge of Python and Fortran. Active and thoughtful listener, adaptable and self-directed worker. Passionate about Data Science and Machine Learning and highly motivated to start my career.



EDUCATION

Physics Degree

University of Barcelona 2019 - Now Machine Learning and Data Science

ZTM Academy 2024 - 2024

Python Developer

ZTM Academy 2023 - 2023

Chemistry Degree

University of Barcelona 2015 - 2020



SKILLS

- Python and Fortran
- Active and thoughtful listener
- Adaptability and self-directed
- Quality Control and Compliance
- International Trade and Imports



PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

QC System Technician

Boehringer Ingelheim

Nov 2021 – Sep 2022

- Preparation and implementation of prescription analysis, analytical methods, material specifications and stability studies so laboratories could make the corresponding analysis.
- Administration and creation of technical working plans using GBS module (SAP) so laboratories could introduce their data into the system.
- Inspection and compliance of laboratory equipment.

Purchasing Intern

Kao Corporation

Apr 2021 – Oct 2021

- Collaboration with air and maritime traffic import procedures and management of the corresponding documentation for customs clearance.
- Data and system administration using SAP.
- Analyse compliance with purchase specifications and define aligned action plans.

R&D Intern

Recam Làser

Iun 2020 - Iul 2020

• Design and development of an engine for the analysis of exhaust gases and implementation of new anti-pollution filters.

QC Intern

Boehringer Ingelheim

Jul 2019 - Apr 2020

- Preparation of the procedures for prescription analysis and analytical methods for the laboratories.
- Ensure compliance of the laboratories against external and internal regulations.



PROJECTS

- Large Language Model Application for Q&A for private documents using OpenAI, Pinecone and LangChain and creation of a front end using Streamlit.
- Password Checker that scans if a given password has ever been hacked by using a password API.
- List of best rated stories from Hacker News website by grabbing and displaying the links using BeautifulSoup library.